Zata.
Truth.
It began long before us.
We who now live our perfect and dull endless lives.
It began long before these moon palaces and body markets
hurling around our golden sun.
It began long before our light-coil thinkers,
our radiation wars,
our oil,
smoke.
It began with us,
the continuity and its twin wanderlust.
The need for unseen shores deep in our marrow.
No judge,
just a queen or king can escape this old blood.
We are no mads,
eternal.
And when no ocean,
mountain,
or sky could contain us,
our gaze hungered star-word.
A far,
they mocked us with their brittle light,
winking and jeering like dangling items,
forever out of reach,
illuminating the truth.
In mortal, as we are,
we die with the sun.
That's where I come in.